chinahighlights.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy and Security, TRUSTe Certificated - China Highlights

Last Updated on **November 25, 2013**

This privacy statement applies to http://www.chinahighlights.com owned and operated by Guilin China International Travel Service Co. Ltd ("China Highlights"). This privacy statement describes how China Highlights collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.chinahighlights.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

China Highlights has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy statement or practices, please contact us at China Highlights, No.11 Binjiang Road, Guilin, China 541002 or email to service@chinahighlights.com.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://www.chinahighlights.com and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site. ****

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, nationality, phone number, zip code
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number
  * Passport and Visa data

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. In addition, we may use website analytics tools, or other technologies, like cookies and web beacons, to collect information about your visit to the Sites, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the Sites and services.

We use this information to

  * Respond to customer service & offer requests 
  * Administer your account
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * To obtain airline tickets and hotel bookings & to apply for travel permits in certain regions in China (Tibet, Hong Kong and Macau)
  * To design a fabulous trip to your best interests
  * Send our latest newsletter to you as your request

### Information Obtained from Third Parties 

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service or booking air tickets. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if China Highlights is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to any personal information for consistency you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

We use cookie in our hotel & flights pages, order forms and account login pages, we set a persistent cookie to store the check in/out date selection, password and some information that you filled, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you can still use our site, but you may enter the same information many times. 

#### Tracking Technologies & Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by our tracking utility company, service providers are not covered by our privacy statement.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc. 

We use Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service, which uses cookies to track non-personal information about our visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by China Highlights only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party.  
We also

#### Web beacons 

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

We use a third party (Google analytics) to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.

#### Flash LSOs

We use local storage objects (LSOs) to store content information and preferences [or – other uses]. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use LSOs to collect and store information.

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html.

#### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from China Highlights. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our website (www.chinahighlightstravel.com), we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at China Highlights, [service@chinahighlights.com](mailto:service@chinahighlights.com).

### Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. send the free e-cards, watch the videos, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it. 

Our Web site offers publicly community forums like travel stories and reviews sharing. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

You can link to our site using social networking services such as Facebook, Twitter, TripAdvisor, Lonelyplanet and Wiki. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your sign-in information, name and email address to link between the sites. Services like Facebook & Twitter give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Tell-A-Friend: If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site or send free e-cards to your friends, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. China Highlights stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at service@chinahighlights.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

With your consent we may post your testimonials, questions and reviews along with your name.  If you want your testimonials, questions and reviews removed please contact us at China Highlights, service@chinahighlights.com.

### Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information 

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, you may contact us directly at [service@chinahighlights.com](mailto:service@chinahighlights.com).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at service@chinahighlights.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes 

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Our Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

**China Highlights, No.11 Binjiang Road, Guilin, China 541002**  
**Email:** [service@chinahighlights.com](mailto:service@chinahighlights.com)

### Choice/Opt-Out 

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletters by the unsubscribe instructions contained in the each newsletter that we sent, or go to our newsletter page on our website, logging into your account and updating your selections or you can contact us at China Highlights, service@chinahighlights.com.

We also allow you to create an account, and share information such as messages, questions, comments, & travel experience with others.
